so glad we could bring this project to
this neighborhood it's so rich in
history
i grew up in a neighborhood like this oh
yeah i i grew up in a neighborhood
exactly like this
all right welcome to mama sugar backs
y'all ready to order yeah can i have a
chicken fried steak with gravy and a
cola
i will have the baked beef short ribs
with collard greens and throw down some
of that cornbread
all right babe
you know what
hold up a second i'm also going to have
some of them collard greens and
cornbread as well but hook a brother up
with some of them hotlinks all right all
right
you know what uh what am i trying to
front scratch all that give me some okra
and some fried red snapper and girl you
know i want some chilies all right man
y'all got ham hocks
of course well that's what i want i want
to play the ham hocks deep fried
blackened and served on a bed of mustard
greens pig feet
i want some pig feet and four pounds of
grits oh oh and you know what else give
me a little dixie cup full of lard all
right i just remember what i want a bowl
of mosquitoes none of them tiny ones
either give me them big to
find down at the swamp sister
could you please hook a brother up with
a rusty bucket full of fish heads
wrapped in razor wire dunk your teeth
dunk your teeth straight out a donkey's
mouth you know what okay any animal
tooth will do i want you to stick it in
some honey glaze fry it with fat back
and serve it in an old tin coffee can
forget everything i said up to this
point right now bring me some dandelion
greens a cow hip and a dog face wrap
that whole mess in an old ebony magazine
and serve it to me in a shoe box okay i
want a platter of stork ankles an old
cellar door a possum spine and a human
foot
you want a human foot
[Music]
i got just one question for y'all
you want gravy on that cellar though
oh definitely oh yeah yeah you got it
for graveyard then you want to sell the
door without gravy it's not food
it's really
[Music]